{
  "description": "Entity label mapping for LSTM-CRF feature extraction across all datasets",
  "version": "1.0",
  "mapping": {
    "PERSON_NAME": "PERSON_NAME",
    "GIVENNAME1": "PERSON_NAME",
    "GIVENNAME2": "PERSON_NAME",
    "LASTNAME1": "PERSON_NAME",
    "LASTNAME2": "PERSON_NAME",
    "LASTNAME3": "PERSON_NAME",
    "TITLE": "PERSON_NAME",
    "USERNAME": "PERSON_NAME",
    "PERSON_TITLE": "PERSON_NAME",
    
    "BOD": "DATE",
    "BIRTHDATE": "DATE",
    "DATE": "DATE",
    
    "CITY": "LOCATION",
    "STATE": "LOCATION", 
    "COUNTRY": "GPE",
    "POSTCODE": "LOCATION",
    "STREET": "LOCATION",
    "BUILDING": "LOCATION",
    "BUILDING_NUMBER": "LOCATION",
    "GEOCOORD": "LOCATION",
    "GEO_COORD": "LOCATION",
    "SECADDRESS": "LOCATION",
    "SEC_ADDRESS": "LOCATION",
    "LOCATION": "LOCATION",
    "ADDRESS": "LOCATION",

    "ORGANIZATION": "ORGANIZATION",
    "ORG": "ORGANIZATION",
    "CARD_ISSUER": "ORGANIZATION",

    "GEOPOLITICAL_ENTITIES": "GPE",
    "GPE": "GPE",

    "NATIONAL_ORIGIN RACE PROTECTED_GROUP": "NORP",
    "NATIONAL_ORIGIN_RACE_PROTECTED_GROUP": "NORP",
    "NORP": "NORP",
    
    "MISC": "0",
    "MISCELLANEOUS": "0",
    "OTHER": "0"
  },
  "target_labels": [
    "PERSON_NAME",
    "PHONE_NUMBER",
    "SOCIAL_NUMBER", 
    "DRIVER_LICENSE",
    "ID_CARD",
    "PASSPORT",
    "CARD_ISSUER",
    "BIRTHDATE",
    "CITY",
    "STATE", 
    "COUNTRY",
    "POSTCODE",
    "STREET",
    "BUILDING_NUMBER",
    "GEO_COORD",
    "SEC_ADDRESS", 
    "ADDRESS",
    "PASSWORD",
    "EMAIL",
    "SEX",
    "0"
  ],
  "dataset_compatibility": {
    "Ai4privacyPii": [
      "PERSON_NAME", "LOCATION", "0", "ORGANIZATION", "DATE", "NORP", "MISC", "GPE"
    ],
    "Conll2003": [
      "PERSON_NAME", "LOCATION", "ORGANIZATION", "MISC"
    ],
    "Ontonotes5": [
      "PERSON_NAME", "LOCATION", "0", "ORGANIZATION", "DATE", "NORP", "MISC", "GPE"
    ],
    "CDR": [
      "MISC"
    ],
    "AFD": [
      "PERSON_NAME", "LOCATION", "ORGANIZATION", "0", "GPE"
    ],
    "LeNERbr": [
      "PERSON_NAME", "GPE", "0"
    ]
  },
  "unmapped_fallback": "0"
}
